George Wilson Todd

About Me Contact Me

I am a final year BA Film Production student at the University of Portsmouth, with plans to do MA Graphic Design next year. My main areas of interest are anime, film and game marketing for both media and merchandising.

I am the current Head of Design & Social Media for the university magazine *Spyglass*. In this job I have worked on illustration, graphic design, writting and editing articles for the magazine, before and during being appointed to my position.

georgetc62@gmail.com

www.vientrisi.com

🣞 07928 798549

Work Experience

Head of Design & Social Media

Spyglass magazine • May 2022 - Present

I oversee the visual content and look of the Spyglass website, articles, social media pages and online editions. I have also illustrated and written/ edited articles for the magazine on several occasions, including before I was appointed to my position.

Crew Member

McDonalds • Jun 2022 - Present

This role improved my communication & team work skills. It has also proved that I can work efficiently, managing several tasks under pressure at peak times.

Education

3rd year of BA Film Production

University of Portsmouth • 2020 - Present (predicted 2.1)

A-Levels

Barton Court Grammar School, Canterbury Film Studies, French and History (CCD)

10 GCSEs

Barton Court Grammar School, Canterbury Including, English Language, Literature & Maths (6s)
Distinction* in the ECDL

Skills

I am proficient in **Procreate** and have some experience using the **Adobe CC** suite as well as other similar programs such as **Affinity Designer**. I have a good understanding of **Figma** which I use to create website mockups. I read and speak **French** at an intermediate level and understand **German** & **Italian** at beginner levels.

References

References can be provided upon request.